<Controls>
    <DateTextBox>
        <Member name="Class">
<remarks>

<h4>Date Fields and Calendar Popup Help</h4>
Date fields support entry of values without the separators. The
fields will automatically attempt to determine the proper placement of
the separators and insert them for you.  For example, if you enter
"102603", it will be reformatted to "10/26/2003".  Date fields also have
a popup calendar that can be accessed by double clicking the date field
or single clicking the calendar icon to the right of the date field as
shown here:<br/><br/>

<img src="../Images/Calendar.bmp" alt="Calendar Popup Icon" />

<p/>Date fields also support the following special key presses:
<ul>
<li><b>T</b> - Insert today's date</li>
<li><b>P</b> - Invoke the calendar popup</li>
<li><b>Page Up</b> - Add a month the date in the field</li>
<li><b>Page Down</b> - Subtract a month from the date in the field</li>
<li><b>Home</b> - Add a year to the date in the field</li>
<li><b>End</b> - Subtract a month from the date in the field</li>
<li><b>Up Arrow</b> - Add a day to the date in the field</li>
<li><b>Down Arrow</b> - Subtract a day from the date in the field</li>
</ul>

<p/>To select a date from the calendar popup, just click on one of the
numbered cells.  To cancel the popup without selecting a date, click the
"X" in the upper right corner or hit the Escape key.  The popup has
dropdown lists that can be used to select a different month and year as
well as the following controls in the top row to navigate in the
calendar:

<ul>
<li><b>&lt;&lt;</b> Previous year</li>
<li><b>&lt;</b> Previous month</li>
<li><b>*</b> - Go to today's month</li>
<li><b>&gt;</b> - Next month</li>
<li><b>&gt;&gt;</b> - Next year</li>
</ul>

<p/>The date selected on entry is highlighted in blue.

</remarks>
        </Member>
    </DateTextBox>

    <NumericTextBox>
        <Member name="Class">
<remarks>
Numeric fields that have decimal places support entry of values without
the decimal point. The fields will automatically attempt to determine
the proper placement of the decimal point and insert it for you.  For
example, if you enter "10" and the field has three decimal places, it
will be reformated to "10.000".  If you enter "10.1", it will be
reformatted to "10.100".  If the <b>InsertDecimal</b> property is set to
true, the decimal point will be inserted into the number rather than the
decimal places being appended.  For example, entering "10" or "101"
would result in the number being reformatted to "0.010" or "0.101"
respectively if the decimal places property were set to three.

</remarks>
        </Member>
    </NumericTextBox>

    <PatternTextBox>
        <Member name="Class">
<remarks>
<h4>The Phone Number, SSN, Time, and Zip Code Patterns</h4>
Fields using the <b>Phone</b>, <b>PhoneNoExt</b>, <b>AreaPhone</b>,
<b>AreaPhNoExt</b>, <b>SSN</b>, <b>Time</b>, <b>ZIP</b>, or <b>ZIP4</b>
patterns support entry of values without the separators. The fields will
automatically attempt to determine the proper placement of the
separators and insert them for you.  For example, if you enter "1530" in
a time field, it will be reformatted to "15:30" when you exit the field.
If you enter "2pm", it will be reformatted to "02:00pm".  If you enter
"999121234" into an SSN field, it will be reformatted to "999-12-1234".

<p/>Time fields also support the following special key presses:
<ul>
<li><b>N</b> - Insert the current time</li>
<li><b>Page Up</b> - Add an hour to the time in the field</li>
<li><b>Page Down</b> - Subtract an hour from the time in the field</li>
<li><b>Up Arrow</b> - Add a minute to the time in the field</li>
<li><b>Down Arrow</b> - Subtract a minute from the time in the field</li>
</ul>

</remarks>
        </Member>
    </PatternTextBox>
    <MaskTextBox>
        <Member name="Class">
<remarks>
The <b>MaskTextBox</b> is similar to the <see cref="PatternTextBox"/> when
used with its <b>Custom</b> pattern type.  The difference is that the
<b>MaskTextBox</b> allows you to specify a mask rather than a regular
expression to define the validation pattern.  This makes it easier to
use than the <b>PatternTextBox</b> with the <b>Custom</b> pattern type.
In addition, mask characters are automatically inserted as the user
types text into the control when rendered on Internet Explorer.  See the
<see cref="Mask"/> property for the mask special characters and their
meanings.
</remarks>
        </Member>
        <Member name="Mask">
<remarks>
The following mask characters can be used in the mask string.  The
control uses mask characters similar to those found in Microsoft Access.
<br/><br/>
<list type="table">
    <listheader>
        <term>Mask Character</term>
        <description>Description</description>
    </listheader>
    <item>
        <term>\ (backslash)</term>
        <description>Causes the character that follows to be displayed as
the literal character.  For example, \A is displayed as just A.  To
include a literal backslash in the mask, use \\.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
        <term>0</term>
        <description>Digit 0 to 9, entry required, plus [+] and minus [-]
signs not allowed.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
        <term>9</term>
        <description>Digit or space, entry optional, plus and minus signs
not allowed.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
        <term>#</term>
        <description>Digit or space, entry optional, plus and minus signs
allowed.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
        <term>L</term>
        <description>Letter A to Z or a to z, entry required.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
        <term>?</term>
        <description>Letter A to Z or a to z, entry optional.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
        <term>A</term>
        <description>Letter or digit, entry required.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
        <term>a</term>
        <description>Letter or digit, entry optional.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
        <term>&amp;</term>
        <description>Any character, entry required.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
        <term>C</term>
        <description>Any character, entry optional.</description>
    </item>
</list>

<p/>The mask characters that indicate that entry is optional can be left
off of text entered into the control as long as no literal characters or
mask characters that have required entry behavior follow them.  For
example, in the mask "aA", the "a" position is actually a required
character because the "A" mask character following it requires entry.

<p/>On a similar note, in a sequence of optional entry mask characters,
only trailing characters can be omitted from the entered text.  For
example, in the mask "##C", the two "#" mask character entries must be
made before the "C" mask character entry can be made.

<p/>If a literal character preceeds a sequence of optional characters, it
will be appended to the text of the control.  For example, if the mask
"00000-9999" is used, if the user enters "12345", the literal "-" will
be appended resulting in the text "12345-" being returned.  If you do
not want the trailing literal character, you must remove it yourself.
This is necessary as the control cannot determine for itself whether a
literal is an optional or required part of the mask.

</remarks>
        </Member>
    </MaskTextBox>
</Controls>
